export const quiz = {
	totalQuestions: 5,
	questions: [
		
        {
            id: 1,
            question: "When Jung is sick, what does he want to eat?",
            answers: ['Sushi', 'Mystery Jelly Beans', 'Rice Porridge', 'McDonalds'],
            correctAnswer: 'Rice Porridge',
		},

		{
            id: 2,
            question: "What does Jung remove from his Mcdonalds Cheeseburgers?",
            answers: ['Pickles', 'Onions', 'Cheese', 'The Bun'],
            correctAnswer: 'Pickles',
		},

        {
            id: 3,
            question: "What university did Jung graduate from?",
            answers: ['Georgia Tech', 'Emory', 'Juliard', 'MIT'],
            correctAnswer: 'Emory',
		},

        {
            id: 4,
            question: "What is the most accurate description of Jung and Travis' relationship?",
            answers: ['Arch-Enemies', 'Work Colleagues', 'Best Friends', 'A Fake Rivalry to Hide The Beautiful Bromance'],
            correctAnswer: 'A Fake Rivalry to Hide The Beautiful Bromance',
		},

        {
            id: 5,
            question: "What is Jung's petname for his girlfriend?",
            answers: ['Love', 'My lil Sushi Roll', 'Wife', 'Honey'],
            correctAnswer: 'Honey',
		},

	]
};

export const coleQuiz = {
	totalQuestions: 5,
	questions: [
		
        {
            id: 1,
            question: "What is Cole going to do when the Bootcamp ends?",
            answers: ['Revel in Unemployment', 'Cry', 'Anxiously Await for Starfield to Come Out', 'All of the Above'],
            correctAnswer: 'All of the Above',
		},

		{
            id: 2,
            question: "What was Cole's Favorite Lunch During the Class Lunchbreaks?",
            answers: ['Wontons with Rice', 'Last Nights Dinner', 'No Lunch for Cole', 'A Simple PB&J'],
            correctAnswer: 'Wontons with Rice',
		},

        {
            id: 3,
            question: "What School Did Cole drop out of in 2017?",
            answers: ['College of Charleston', 'University of Georgia', 'MIT', 'University of South Carolina'],
            correctAnswer: 'University of South Carolina',
		},

        {
            id: 4,
            question: "How Many Pets Does Cole Have?",
            answers: ['Zero', 'One', 'Two', 'Three'],
            correctAnswer: 'Two',
		},

        {
            id: 5,
            question: "How has Cole Stayed Enerized During Class for the Last Three Months?",
            answers: ['Coffee', 'Mio Energy', 'Energy Drinks', 'Coke'],
            correctAnswer: 'Mio Energy',
		}

	]
};